McKersie, Robert Nassau County Multi-Municipality Productivity Project Files 6327
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Robert McKersie Nassau County Multi-Municipality Productivity Project Files
1972- 1975
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
McKersie, Robert
Nassau County
6327
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
7506531
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 14, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 26, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Collective bargaining; McKersie, Robert B.
7506531
- Reports, Correspondence, Handwritten notes (Box 1)
  - County Officers Association of the State of New York, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Productivity Bargaining Session 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Vince Macri - Memorandums, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Productivity, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Vince J. Macri, Papers, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Vincent J. Macri - Letters, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ralph Caso, Nassau, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - MMPP, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - MMPP, letters from Vincent J. Macri, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Notes (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - MMPP & Nassau Council, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Nassau, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Vincent J. Macri, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - MMPP Survey Program, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Vincent J. Macri, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Nassau, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Nassau County, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - County Executive's Office; Vince Macri, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Nassau - Notes, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Vince Macri - Misc., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Notes, 1973-1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Nassau County MMPP, 1941-1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Forms, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Notes & Status Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Nassau, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Nassau, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - My prod. Paper, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Nassau County Vincent J Macri, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Memorandums, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Macri - Articles, Notes, Memos, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - MMPP & other Productivity Commissions, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 31)